# Moe Ayoub

2421 E Irwin St, Pierre SD, 57501 | +1(605)-740-5024 | mma.ayoub@outlook.com

## **Summary**

As a Full Stack Developer, I led the development of an Agricultural Division's E-Commerce website and integrated multiple systems using technologies like C#, Azure, Boomi, and Oracle. My expertise lies in object-oriented programming, and web development, where I focus on creating user-friendly solutions to optimize complex system performance.

### **Skills**

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, C#, Python, Java, C++, C

Frontend: HTML, CSS, SASS, Tailwind, Vue.js, React.js, Nuxt.js, Next.js

Backend: Microsoft SOL Server, Oracle SOL, Postgre SOL, MySOL, Azure Functions, Node.js

Platforms: Azure, Salesforce, Boomi, IFS ERP

Tools: Git, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, PyCharm, Postman

## **Experience**

## **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | RAVEN INDUSTRIES INC | OCT 2020 - SEPT 2023**

- Integrated our E-Commerce web site to Raven's new ERP system. Utilizing C#, Azure Web App, Message Service Bus Queues, Web Job, Microsoft SQL Server, and Oracle SQL
- Integrated our 3rd party CRM (Salesforce) system with Raven's current ERP system. Utilizes C#, Boomi, and Oracle. Then re-did the integration by building a .NET library (SOAP) for Salesforce and creating .NET console apps to sync data between Raven's current ERP and Salesforce
- Integrated our IT ticketing system (Ivanti) with Azure DevOps by building a .NET 6 console app
- Developed Salesforce LWC, Aura, and APEX classes to enhance Raven's business processes

## **BUSINESS ANALYST | FLEXON TECHNOLOGIES | JUNE 2020 - AUG 2020**

- In-depth knowledge of Software Development Life Cycle
- Extensive experience with SCRUM to accommodate requirement changes and promote flexibility
- Ability to elicit, analyze, gather, document, and prioritize requirements and specifications for complex and simple projects

### SENIOR DESIGN PROJECT | DAKTRONICS | AUG 2019 - MAY 2020

- Designed a device that can gain physical access to the network settings of Daktronics's display controllers (host device) and to reconfigure those network settings as needed
- Responsible for programming the microprocessor and the C# application that allows the microprocessor to communicate with the host device
- Created a setup file for the C# application for easy installation of the C# application.
- Designed and built the PCB for the device

## APPLICATION ENGINEER INTERN | SENCORE INC | MAY 2018 - AUG 2019

- Led the software and hardware testing for Sencore and WELLAV products to ensure products met or exceeded specifications.
- Responsible for determining the root cause of customer reported issues and reporting the results to the Application Engineering team for resolution.
- Collaborated with the Engineering department to enhance the stability and performance of development products.

#### TECHNICIAN | SDSU PERFORMING ARTS CENTER | SEPT 2017 - MAY 2018

- Responsible for running wires to the stage speakers and setting up the lighting system.
- Troubleshooting defective equipment during live performances.

#### Education

## SOUTH DAKOTA STATE UNIVERSITY | BACHELOR OF SCIENCE DEGREE | AUG. 2015 - MAY 2020

Major: Electrical Engineering

Minors: Mathematics

# **Projects**

## **MOVIESAPP | FEB 2024 | REPO-LINK**

A collection of movies and shows (similar to IMDB). Built with Nuxt.js, TypeScript and Tailwind

## FAKESTORE | DEC 2023 | REPO-LINK

An E-Commerce website built with Vue.js, SASS, and JavaScript. Features include user management & store checkout. Powered by Azure & Supabase. For the purposes of this demo, the Best Buy API was used to display products on the E-Commerce website

### RESUME WEBSITE | NOV 2023 | REPO-LINK

My personal web resume made with Vue.js, SASS, JavaScript, Azure Functions, and C#

#### **Certificates**

### ASSOCIATE INTEGRATION DEVELOPER

• Boomi - OCT 2023

#### **C# CERTIFICATE**

• HackerRank – <u>CERT-LINK</u> – OCT 2023

#### **JAVA CERTIFICATE**

• HackerRank – <u>CERT-LINK</u> – OCT 2023

#### **PYTHON CERTIFICATE**

• HackerRank – <u>CERT-LINK</u> – OCT 2023

## JAVASCRIPT CERTIFICATE

HackerRank – CERT-LINK – OCT 2023

## **SQL CERTIFICATE**

• HackerRank – <u>CERT-LINK</u> – OCT 2023